为了构建我们的ui 我们来从MainActivity的
To build out our UI, let's start with the wire
框图开始  它展示了一个天气预报的列表
frame for the main activity. It displays a list of
每个条目保护一个图标 日期 和天气情况
forecasts, where each item contains an icon, a date, weather
也有最高和最低温度
description; as well as high and low temperatures for that
由于今天的天气是用户关注最高的
day. Since today's weather is probably most relevant to the
我们给了它更突出的显示相比于
user, we give more prominence to it as a list
另外日期的天气 我们将开始构建列表的条目在
item compared to the other days. We'll start off by
接下来的几天里 因为它是比较简单的
building the list item layout for future days because it's simpler.
然后再开始构建今天的列表条目
And then afterwards, we'll come back to do the today layout.
在当前的实现中 列表的条目xml布局是
In the current implementation, the list item forecast layout XML is
一个含有4个TextView的LinearLayout 我们也需要再修改这个布局
a horizontal linear layout of four text views. We'll need to
以达到框图要求的效果
modify the layout so that it looks like this wire frame.
我们应该一个一个来指导我们掌握了ViewGroup的几个布局
We should divide and conquer until we can use the view
的用法 你能想象一下
group layouts that we're familiar with. Can you imagine how you'd
来把这个ui分解成你所知道的组件吗?
break down this UI into components that you know how to
作为一个提示 如果我在这画一些分割线呢
build? As a hint, what if I draw these separators here?
你能找到一个方法
Within those elements, can you find a way to
更近一步的进行分解用相应的ViewGroup
break it down even further with view groups you're familiar
你将使用到嵌套的view组 意味着view组里面有子view组
with? You'll need nested view groups, which means view groups
提示一下  这些数据是动态改变的
with children view groups. As a tip, this data will
但是你可以
be populated dynamically at run time. But you can
为了测试先写死一些值就像明天的日期或者
test it by hard coding some text values such as
清楚的气象条件
Tomorrow for the date or Clear for the weather condition.
对于图片 我们指定一个叫做ic_launcher的文件名
For images, we can specify a placeholder drawable called ic_launcher.
之所以这样命名 意味它是一个启动的图标 也叫做应用的
It's named this way, because it's the launcher icon, which is also
icon 这已经被包含到我们的app中了
known as the app icon. And this is already included in our
我们将得到天气的图标在之后的课程里
app. We'll be getting the rest of our weather icons for our
如果你想看下这个布局的样子
app later in this lesson. If you want to see what this layout
你可以点击设备窗格看一下预览
looks like, you can click on the design pane to see a
在右侧 我们看到一个树形展示了不同的view
preview of it. On the right, we see a component tree listing
我们也可以看一个给定的view的属性和值
out the different views. We can also see for a given view
我们可以改变设备的方向当你预览的时候
what the properties are, and their values. We can change the orientation
你也可以选择不同的设备就像
of the device that your previewing, you can also
Nexus 7 或Nexus系列的
select different devices such as Nexus 7, or Nexus
你也可以同时预览多个设备
10. You can also preview multiple devices at the
当你构建你的布局的时候
same time. As you build out your layout for
不要担心字体的颜色或者大小
this task, don't worry about the font color, or
或者之后的任何视觉细节
font size, or any other visual details until later.
当你编译并且允许后 应用应该看起来像这样
After you compile and run, the app should look
选择这个框当你完成的时候
something like this. Check this box when you're done.